Uh. our info is limited.
these guys aren't in our database.
All we really know is that they came
from Guangzhou. China.
I'm still investigating
to get the exact details.
How close are we on the server?
I still got. uh. two-thirds or more?
And the shopping mall migration?
Seventy percent.
It's 'cause we're only working nights.
We have to avoid any tracking by Babylon.
I have to go get Jian myself.
Those bastards are gonna
go after her quickly.
What's that?
I think they already found us.
Can't get a clear shot.
Container's in the way.
As expected.
Hold your positions.
We're going in.
Listen carefully.
Put your personal grudge aside.
Jeong Jinman has
to be captured alive. Translate.
Jeong Jinman needs
to be captured alive. sir.
He has to be alive.
Just don't get in my way.
You'll die first. Translate.
Ah. shit.
Uh… what he said was…
Ah. die first?
I didn't get the last part.
What?
That… one-eyed bastard…
Appreciate you working so late.
We can begin now.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 04
RAID
Understood.
I will retrieve the asset
and put things back in order.
Who is it?
Who could make the great Kusanagi act
so submissively. huh?
I can keep on climbing higher and higher.
but there's always another level.
Don't you miss fieldwork?
Not at all.
The smell of blood…
…and gunpowder just stays in your nose.
Ugh.
I'd rather be a knight than a pawn anyway.
Or even better. I could be the one
who designs the board in the first place.
As for capturing Jeong Jinman.
you need to be the one to do it.
I like the sound of that.
And Q?
Q will…
…get rattled.
I need the one who leads this team
to be someone cold.
Hmm…
Women's intuition.
Smoke!
Don't panic. Hold your positions.
He's the most skilled agent
in your team.
Don't you think it's long overdue
for J to lead a unit?
I don't think it's combat skills
that determines a good leader.
If the target's Jeong Jinman.
I think it does.
That's not it.
I'm talking about Bale.
Bale's just a hunting dog at this point.
If you take him off his leash.
he'll find Jinman for us.
We should be using that.
Working with Bale to capture Jinman
was actually J's choice as team leader.
You can't keep coddling him forever
because he's your little brother.
J has the skills he needs.
Branch Chief…
are you and my brother
still seeing each other?
Heavy radio signal detected.
Remove it.
If you really cared about Jun…
why stick him with a time bomb like Bale…
and send him after Jeong Jinman?
If you're afraid of things like that.
you're in the wrong line of work entirely.
You should try going back
to being yakuza again.
Or open a bar in Dotonbori
and leave the dangerous missions to us.
Hey. Japanese.
- It's a trap.
- What?
If they hid the server
in a place like this.
wouldn't it mean they're prepared
to bolt at any moment?
What are you doing?
Translate it.
If they hid the server
in a place like this.
wouldn't it mean they're prepared
to bolt at any moment?
That's what he's said.
Bravo. Tango.
find dead ends of containers
that can be connected
to the current Alpha position.
and identify all trucks. cranes.
and modes of transportation
within a 100-meter radius.
Possible ambush on Tango.
J. forget about Tango.
Hey. didn't you say it was a trap?
What are you doing? Translate it.
If it's a trap. we don't go in?
Are you scared?
That's right. the enemy of my enemy
should be my friend.
After you.
Grenade!
Marco. Marco!
I'm okay.
I'll be right back.
Jinman's here. that slick fuck.
Bravo. current location?
After you.
It's a trap.
That hurts!
Shit.
Long time. no see.
Jeong Jinman.
I'm just sorry we have to meet like this.
J. don't forget.
We need Jeong Jinman alive.
What the hell's that moron doing?
I told you we have to capture him alive!
I thought I made it clear to you.
If you get in my way. you'll die first.
Shit.
Ugh…
Move it.
Shit.
Look! Over there!
Snipers. what are you doing?
Hurry up and stop that truck.
Move to ten o'clock now!
We're out of time. let's haul ass!
You always did have something up
your sleeve. Jinman.
Always so petty.
Just ram through it!
Hold on to something!
All these clever little tricks
are only gonna blow up in your face.
Jeong Jinman. I'll see you in hell...
Tell me.
are we being recorded
in the command center?
No. ma'am.
We don't record
unofficial internal operations.
Good work. everybody.
You can all go home.
Q's operation is in a few hours.
What's our angle here?
Hmm…
I'll figure something out.
I'm starving.
Can you handle it?
Can I get room service?
Even though Bale's a psycho.
how could he kill his own team like that?
Dying like a dog as soon
as you leave Japan…
I heard that J was Q's younger brother.
That hurts!
- Yeah?
- Everything is set.
But there are two employees
from another department
and the bus driver on board.
I think that…
looks more natural. don't you think?
Whoo!
Good job. K.
You understand?
Jeong Jinman was the one who killed J.
Bale didn't do it.
We have to make sure
that Q never discovers the truth
under any circumstances.
This… stays between us.
Fortunately.
the residents had all left the island.
Your friend Miss Arin rushed to Seoul
because of her uncle's sudden passing.
And it looks like she won't be able
to come back.
We'll make it
so nothing happened here tonight.
So. as long as you keep quiet.
that's the end of it.
You'll be free to return
to your normal life.
However.
once Miss Jian leaves here.
you'll be strangers from that moment on.
Any contact is forbidden.
Hey. I don't think that's necess…
That's going too far.
Woojin…
If you need help.
you can contact me at this number.
CO.. Ltd. JAEWON CLEANING
Team Leader Kim Jaewon
Arin…
No.
Your real name is…
Jian. isn't it?
I don't think
I'll be any help cleaning here.
Let me know when it's all done.
I'll be at the house.
Woojin. wait.
Do you think it's okay to let him leave.
just like that?
There are traces of him
having accessed the app data.
When you catch up. what are you gonna say?
That boy Woojin…
do you like him?
Stay level-headed.
You remember Bae Jeongmin. right?
- We don't know who'll come looking and...
- Unni…
I'm really hungry.
Why don't we eat something?
We got some mumallaengi.
Auntie Soonae grows the radishes.
dries and seasons them herself.
It's so good.
And these are bangiip muchin and myeolchi
that Auntie Pilsun made.
And this one…
Auntie Jeomrye. she found out
I liked sausage and stir-fried vegetables.
so she made this for me.
Ah…
Meongge-jeot…
Auntie Jeomrye's specialty.
Jian.
we don't have time to be doing this.
This stuff…
I've never…
I never got to just be like this
with Uncle.
After getting here…
living a normal life like everyone else.
it was just really nice.
Having someone there for me…
and me being there for them too.
Laughing together.
making meals.
just talking…
normal.
A normal life. you know?
Living a normal life
like everyone else gets to.
Until yesterday. I really…
…really believed
I could keep going like this.
Look. your uncle really tried.
He did everything he could for you. Jian.
I know he did. I know that.
I found a way here
to live life on my own terms.
It's better than that cage he kept me in
'cause it was dangerous.
And that was his past catching up to us.
It had nothing at all to do with me.
Even still…
if you were to stay here.
Woojin and everyone around you
will all be in danger.
I know that.
I'll go back to my uncle. I just…
Could we just…
have one moment?
Can we have one more meal
as normal people first?
WOOJIN
Team Leader. she isn't alone.
How should we handle this?
You can eliminate anyone
who gets in your way.
Just get her.
And for our extraction?
We can transport you on our ship.
This is bad.
You have to go now!
Woojin. is there another way to the docks?
On the back side of the island.
there's a way there.
Listen carefully.
I'll stay and stall them as long as I can.
Head to the docks with Woojin.
Once you get down there.
find the boat called the JW.
Director Kim. give them cover.
Right. I'm on it.
Unni.
I'll be fine.
Listen. your unni will never die.
They're coming!
Team Leader. there's a four-wheeler
headed towards the docks.
It looks like Jeong Jian.
Bravo. start making your way in.
Let's roll out.
Are you all right?
We have to hurry and catch up to Jian.
Woojin!
Arin. hold on to me!
Arin…
Arin. get up.
Jeong Jian…
Wait. is that your boat over there?
You can't!
Shit.
This is your last chance.
If you don't come with me. your boyfriend
will also die just like that.
Hey. my boat's right there.
You're her. huh?
So Minhye.
Woojin. hard left now!
Seal it off.
I'm sorry. Woojin.
I'm doing fine.
Look. I'm still in one piece.
So don't worry.
Hey. don't say you forgot.
do you remember my promise?
In Hanam-do.
I won't let anyone
touch even a hair on your head.
I won't let them get the chance.
You're right.
They won't have a chance in hell.
Jian. get down!
Boom.
Give them a warning shot. to wake them up.
Woojin. drop down!
Woojin. Woojin!
It's okay. Just wait a second.
Jeong Jian!
I want Jeong Jian brought in alive.
Jian. hey…
Jeong Jian.
That's your name. right?
Jeong Jian?
Uh-huh.
Even your name is beautiful. Jian.
I…
Hey. didn't I promise you?
Not a single hair.
Not a single hair on your head.
Let me just say…
thanks for hanging out…
with a hick like me.
Woojin. hey!
Don't close your eyes!
No! You can't…
You can't…
Jeong Jinman!
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG